<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[业余项目分享交流]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览reddit业余项目讨论]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 04:36:39 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[How I Made a Wireless, Fast-Change Set Of Headphones On a $40,000 Prototype Budget]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://reddit.com/link/qk00h9/video/703wicvi0vw71/player

The story of modern headphone reliability and convenience is a poem of two words
– it sucks. Headphones wield quite the reputation for being not only rebels in
the behavior of their wire-attachments, but are also quite lousy as…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qk00h9/how_i_made_a_wireless_fastchange_set_of/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qk00h9/how_i_made_a_wireless_fastchange_set_of/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 23:20:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://reddit.com/link/qk00h9/video/703wicvi0vw71/player&quot;&gt;https://reddit.com/link/qk00h9/video/703wicvi0vw71/player&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The story of modern headphone reliability and convenience is a poem of two words – it sucks. Headphones wield quite the reputation for being not only rebels in the behavior of their wire-attachments, but are also quite lousy as companions who can be relied on in times they are most needed. Wired headphones aside, their more advanced brethren are no better in that regard, as batteries run dry near-instantly and are less than adequate for any kind of trip that takes the user beyond the reach of a wall outlet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Everyone nowadays uses some kind of headphones. Be it teenagers for listening to music and streams, to businessmen confined to remote working environments. Such universality also comes with a few downsides, since the main problems and pain points that currently prevent users from being completely satisfied with wireless headphones are common for all audiences and device sectors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The insufficiency of battery life and the remote operational capabilities of headphones are the biggest problems. Not everyone has the luxury of carrying several fully charged sets of headpieces, or has access to a charger when they need it most.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And that’s why I came up with a solution, since I too felt the pain of being left in the dark when the music suddenly ran dry together with the headphones’ battery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A rechargeable battery is fine, but wireless headphones with replaceable batteries that can be changed on-the-go and hassle-free are the Holy Grail of sound technologies. Add to that a stylish look and excellent sound characteristics and you have the makings of a groundbreaking product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just imagine – continuing to hear that crystal clear tune and its vibrations through your entire body with just a short interlude between battery shifts on-the-fly. Glorious and true to the spirit of modern technologies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But it gets better, since I made the headphones waterproof, added in some noise canceling software, and a spruce of touch controls to take them to cyberpunk level. Device compatibility across markets makes the device the pinnacle of modern headphone technologies that are embodied in Relods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Getting there is just the start of the journey as the Indiegogo product crowdfunding campaign has already been launched for Relods, making the Relods headphones a product by the people for the people. Let the users decide what they want – to keep roaming the market in search of that one pair of nonexistent, ideal headphones, or pitch in and get a pair of Relods headphones that include all they ever wanted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The target of $40,000 is a drop in the ocean compared to the value Relods can bring to their users in terms of all-round convenience, prolonged battery life, pristine sound quality, and that ‘oomph’ factor in which form &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; function. Join the Relods crowdfunding campaign &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.indiegogo.com/projects/relods/coming_soon&quot;&gt;on Indiegogo&lt;/a&gt; and let everyone enjoy the benefits of a world of advanced sound technologies free of chargers and unexpected power mishaps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://reddit.com/link/qk00h9/video/24h00zur0vw71/player&quot;&gt;https://reddit.com/link/qk00h9/video/24h00zur0vw71/player&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[SocialBoat - No code platform for fitness creators!]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://www.producthunt.com/posts/socialboat

Hi everyone!

I wanted to share a product with the community that initially started as a side
project. Today we launched it on ProductHunt.

SocialBoat is a no code platform for fitness creators that creates a full
digital suite for fitness…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qjwq0i/socialboat_no_code_platform_for_fitness_creators/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qjwq0i/socialboat_no_code_platform_for_fitness_creators/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 23:20:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.producthunt.com/posts/socialboat&quot;&gt;https://www.producthunt.com/posts/socialboat&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hi everyone!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wanted to share a product with the community that initially started as a side project. Today we launched it on ProductHunt. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SocialBoat is a no code platform for fitness creators that creates a full digital suite for fitness professionals. From a community, fitness tracking, nutrition planning to landing page and marketing automation. We have focussed on a vertical so that we can build specialised tools and template utilities relevant for fitness professionals. Do check us out and upvote if you find value. Thank you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Built a managed API for adding file search to your software]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qjpath/built_a_managed_api_for_adding_file_search_to/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qjpath/built_a_managed_api_for_adding_file_search_to/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 22:42:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I built a platform allowing businesses and individuals to share SMS Multi-Factor Authentication Codes]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hello there Reddit!

I just wanted to share with you a product I've been working on for a while. The
product is called GetMyMfa and is accessible at https://get.mymfa.io. The
objective of this project is to allow organizations to safely and easily share
Multi-Factor Authentication codes for their…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qjublf/i_built_a_platform_allowing_businesses_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qjublf/i_built_a_platform_allowing_businesses_and/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 20:49:11 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello there Reddit!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I just wanted to share with you a product I&amp;#39;ve been working on for a while. The product is called GetMyMfa and is accessible at &lt;a href=&quot;https://get.mymfa.io&quot;&gt;https://get.mymfa.io&lt;/a&gt;. The objective of this project is to allow organizations to safely and easily share Multi-Factor Authentication codes for their Quality Assurance and Apple App Store review processes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Where the idea came from:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am currently working with multiple customers in the FSI domain (Financial Services Industry) and I am often required to perform tests in production and staging environments with multiple accounts. As production and staging accounts, these accounts are generally required to have at least an SMS 2FA system in place. When performing tests in such sensitive accounts, a single individual usually owns all phone numbers linked to these accounts and shares received MFA codes via a phone call with the various people performing tests in these accounts. I believe this represents a security concern and a bypass of the Multi-Factor Authentication principles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition, when submitting iOS applications to the App Store, Apple performs a human review process in which they need to login to the application. When MFA is enforced for all production accounts, Apple rejects the application unless a way is implemented to allow them to login. This often leaves developers with two options: Develop a front-end only demonstration mode, or bypass the MFA mechanism for a specific account.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Therefore, the project aims to:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Allow organizations to rent virtual phone numbers and have their SMS MFA codes be displayed in a private web interface;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Organizations have fine-grained access control allowing them to control who can access their virtual phone numbers MFA Codes;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Access granting to virtual phone numbers can be time-based.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;With this project, I aim to help businesses to:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoid spending time in building a security login &amp;quot;bypass&amp;quot; (and all the security issues that often come with it);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoid building a &amp;quot;demonstration&amp;quot; mode exclusively for Apple on their mobile applications;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Avoid using public websites with public phone numbers accessible to anyone.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What do you think? Would you use such product for your business in order to safely manage SMS Multi-Factor-Authentication sharing in production accounts? I would love hearing your feedback on the pros and cons you see about this product.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All the best, &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jonathan&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[API creation pricing]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hi, I assume that a lot of you work with APIs for your side-projects.

as freelancers that are asked to create an API for a client (or as a client
offering a freelancer work)

how much do you think is fair to charge/pay for creating an API (Code is
provided by the requestor, the work is setting it…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qjodsc/api_creation_pricing/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qjodsc/api_creation_pricing/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 19:18:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi, I assume that a lot of you work with APIs for your side-projects.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;as freelancers that are asked to create an API for a client (or as a client offering a freelancer work)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;how much do you think is fair to charge/pay for creating an API (Code is provided by the requestor, the work is setting it up as an API on a cloud provider including all relevant components (security, API gateway, load balancing etc..)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[https://textfrom.website - I created a one page service to extract texts from web pages.. useful when some websites force you to register to read the contents. Any feedback is welcome.]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qjr4ke/httpstextfromwebsite_i_created_a_one_page_service/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qjr4ke/httpstextfromwebsite_i_created_a_one_page_service/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 16:31:54 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[During my last summer break, I developed Realsteer, a pair of free apps that allow you to use the sensors in an iPhone as a controller to play almost all racing games on PC. It would be great if you could try it out and give me feedback. Here is a short film that I made for it. Enjoy!]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://youtu.be/QNfSx_NinQs]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qjhqwi/during_my_last_summer_break_i_developed_realsteer/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qjhqwi/during_my_last_summer_break_i_developed_realsteer/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 12:12:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/QNfSx_NinQs&quot;&gt;https://youtu.be/QNfSx_NinQs&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[P2P file sharing utility]]></title><description><![CDATA[I created https://dropall.stream/ as a universal simple p2p files sharing
service. Think something like airdrop but universal to any device.

My goal was to make a service where anyone could share a file in not more than 3
clicks. There are no file limits, data is transferred from peer to peer…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qjk3oy/p2p_file_sharing_utility/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qjk3oy/p2p_file_sharing_utility/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 31 Oct 2021 11:07:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I created &lt;a href=&quot;https://dropall.stream/&quot;&gt;https://dropall.stream/&lt;/a&gt; as a universal simple p2p files sharing service. Think something like airdrop but universal to any device. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My goal was to make a service where anyone could share a file in not more than 3 clicks. There are no file limits, data is transferred from peer to peer without any intermediate servers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m looking for feedback and potential collaborators who would be interested in growing the project. IOS and Android apps are in Beta. Ping me if you would like access.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[/meet 4 Slack]]></title><description><![CDATA[Excited to share my first product, a powerful Google Meet <> Slack integration.

Simply generate Google Meets by using /meet command in any DM, group or channel.

🚀 Google Meet links will open with the correct Google Account (selected when
first using the app). This means you no longer have to…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qjc5at/meet_4_slack/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qjc5at/meet_4_slack/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 23:57:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excited to share my first product, a powerful Google Meet &amp;lt;&amp;gt; Slack integration.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Simply generate Google Meets by using /meet command in any DM, group or channel. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🚀 Google Meet links will open with the correct Google Account (selected when first using the app). This means you no longer have to switch between multiple Google accounts (work/personal) before entering a meeting. Solving the Google authuser problem. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🚀 Slack status automatically updates for everyone who joins the meeting. Users can customise the icon, status and duration or turn this off (this feature only works on paid Slack workspaces).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;🚀 Random movie quote with every generated meeting to bring some fun into your calls. Turn off if you want!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;💸 For free, no limits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The app was approved by both Google and Slack and developed with privacy in mind. It will only request the permissions it actually needs to function (no unnecessary user or workspace data).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check it out on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.producthunt.com/posts/meet-for-slack-2&quot;&gt;Product Hunt&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Get it on &lt;a href=&quot;https://projectundefined.com&quot;&gt;the product website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Get notified on Discord when your blog is mentioned on Hacker News]]></title><description><![CDATA[I wanted to study Typescript so I wrote this quick side project that lets you
send Discord messages of Hacker News submissions that match your blog domain.
This can be handy to be notified when others submit some of your content to
Hacker News.

https://github.com/louisguitton/hn-notifier

It's…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qj3wjs/get_notified_on_discord_when_your_blog_is/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qj3wjs/get_notified_on_discord_when_your_blog_is/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 23:57:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I wanted to study Typescript so I wrote this quick side project that lets you send Discord messages of Hacker News submissions that match your blog domain. This can be handy to be notified when others submit some of your content to Hacker News.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/louisguitton/hn-notifier&quot;&gt;https://github.com/louisguitton/hn-notifier&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s completely free, you deploy it to Heroku using the button on the Github Readme, you put in your domain and your personal Discord webhook URL (from a channel of the Discord server you want to see this appear in) and voila!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is less than 100 lines of Typescript code, mostly thanks to the fact that Hacker News&amp;#39; &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/HackerNews/API&quot;&gt;official API&lt;/a&gt; is built around Firebase.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This project is similar to other tools that you might prefer:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;F5Bot&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Google alerts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[My first project]]></title><description><![CDATA[I have been doing my first project in my spare time for several months.

Meet Snappy Form [https://snappy-form.com/], build beautiful online forms for
free. I will be glad to receive feedback and suggestions to make the platform
even better.


FEATURES

 * Integrations
 * Email notifications of new…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qj0a4y/my_first_project/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qj0a4y/my_first_project/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 17:00:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have been doing my first project in my spare time for several months.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meet &lt;a href=&quot;https://snappy-form.com/&quot;&gt;Snappy Form&lt;/a&gt;, build beautiful online forms for free. I will be glad to receive feedback and suggestions to make the platform even better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Features&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Integrations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Email notifications of new responses&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Limited access&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Export responses&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Redirects&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Hidden fields&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Multi-page forms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Customize the styles of forms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;What else to expect&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Logical connections of blocks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Parameters of forms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Teams&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New integrations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Access to a form by password&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New blocks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;More customization features of forms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Pricing&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 forms&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unlimited blocks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Unlimited responses&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;30 days of storing responses&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 integration for form&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Stock Trading Bots]]></title><description><![CDATA[Here is a tool that allows you to build and test stock trading bots quickly. Has
a decent collection of examples and live community.

http://breakingequity.com/]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qiq6ex/stock_trading_bots/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qiq6ex/stock_trading_bots/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 17:00:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here is a tool that allows you to build and test stock trading bots quickly. Has a decent collection of examples and live community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://breakingequity.com/&quot;&gt;http://breakingequity.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Backend as a Service?]]></title><description><![CDATA[I am trying to understand if it worthwhile to create another BaaS since there
are at least 3 similar services: Parse, Firbase and AWS Amplify.

 1. Did you try to use any of these BaaS?
 2. What were the pain points? Installing cli, configuring?
 3. Was it costly for you?
 4. Which functionality was…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qizb45/backend_as_a_service/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qizb45/backend_as_a_service/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 14:19:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am trying to understand if it worthwhile to create another BaaS since there are at least 3 similar services: Parse, Firbase and AWS Amplify. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Did you try to use any of these BaaS?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What were the pain points? Installing cli, configuring?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Was it costly for you? &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Which functionality was missing and you would like to have? &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Will you use the following functionality: upload REST schema file and start using generated end points?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I'm launching a motivational text message service... feedback appreciated!]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hi!

I'm looking to build a variety of "clubs" that offer daily, handcrafted text
messages around a specific topic - this concept can apply to news, memes,
advice, facts, etc. Myself and a few partners are starting off with a Motivation
Club, which offers daily motivational texts, which just…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qinosz/im_launching_a_motivational_text_message_service/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qinosz/im_launching_a_motivational_text_message_service/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 08:49:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m looking to build a variety of &amp;quot;clubs&amp;quot; that offer daily, handcrafted text messages around a specific topic - this concept can apply to news, memes, advice, facts, etc. Myself and a few partners are starting off with a Motivation Club, which offers daily motivational texts, which just launched a few days ago. The website is &lt;a href=&quot;https://motivationclubs.com&quot;&gt;motivationclubs.com&lt;/a&gt; and we&amp;#39;re currently offering 3 months free (normally $1.99 per month) for one motivational text per day. Any feedback on the concept, website, price, product, etc, would be greatly appreciated. Very happy to check out anything you&amp;#39;re working on. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pazly help you make awesome landing pages for your (side) project with just drag and drop. Start free at https://pazly.dev/]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qidu08/pazly_help_you_make_awesome_landing_pages_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qidu08/pazly_help_you_make_awesome_landing_pages_for/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 03:24:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I am building a realistic space colony management game. The story starts in the 1970s, and you can only use actual technology to build your Moon village.]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qimdy3/i_am_building_a_realistic_space_colony_management/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qimdy3/i_am_building_a_realistic_space_colony_management/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 22:09:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[3 years making and I have finally launched a great Personal Finance App]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hi there!

During the last 3 years, on my free time, I have put a lot of effort into
building a personal finance app. Why? I did not like the ones that existed and
also, as a developer, I wanted to study some technologies. So, here it is:
https://www.finansiapp.com

A new personal finance, expense…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qifpz7/3_years_making_and_i_have_finally_launched_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qifpz7/3_years_making_and_i_have_finally_launched_a/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 19:30:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi there!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the last 3 years, on my free time, I have put a lot of effort into building a personal finance app. Why? I did not like the ones that existed and also, as a developer, I wanted to study some technologies. So, here it is: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.finansiapp.com&quot;&gt;https://www.finansiapp.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A new personal finance, expense tracking and budgeting app. Carefully thought out and centered on you. Simple, powerful and constantly evolving. Keep track of your money the easy way, make better decisions and have a healthy financial life. With Finansi App, you have a complete view of your personal finances.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first step to making money is to control your money. Finansi has all you need to organize your finances and more:  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- Categories and subcategories&lt;br/&gt;
- Budgets&lt;br/&gt;
- Bank accounts&lt;br/&gt;
- Cash&lt;br/&gt;
- Credit cards&lt;br/&gt;
- Prepaid cards&lt;br/&gt;
- Notes&lt;br/&gt;
- Pictures and files attachments&lt;br/&gt;
- Tags&lt;br/&gt;
- Location&lt;br/&gt;
- Installments&lt;br/&gt;
- Search&lt;br/&gt;
- Filters&lt;br/&gt;
- Multi currency&lt;br/&gt;
- Export transactions&lt;br/&gt;
- Offline support  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Understand your cash flow. Use budgets to control spending and make better decisions. With Finansi App you have a complete view of your personal finances.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cash, Bank Accounts, Credit Cards and Prepaid Cards: Easily track your transactions, whether they are payments, receivements or transfers. Check your balance and see invoices.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Organize everything into categories and subcategories. Search and find transactions with ease. Set budgets by month or by week. Control your income and expenses.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can take notes, add attachments and record the location of transactions. It is possible to use different currencies and make conversions between them. The app also works offline.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Continuously improving: more features and languages to come.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.finansiapp.com&quot;&gt;Download now&lt;/a&gt; and try it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[An app that reveals trends for every city in the world, on a whole new level]]></title><description><![CDATA[I spent years developing this huge app to reveal trends for every city in the
world, using data that's never been seen before.

The app is based on place geofences, which do not exist anywhere in the world,
and are created within this app by the community.

Imagine hundreds of thousands of people…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qi2jug/an_app_that_reveals_trends_for_every_city_in_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qi2jug/an_app_that_reveals_trends_for_every_city_in_the/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 19:00:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I spent years developing this huge app to reveal trends for every city in the world, using data that&amp;#39;s never been seen before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The app is based on place geofences, which do not exist anywhere in the world, and are created within this app by the community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Imagine hundreds of thousands of people answering questions within thousands of places, with near 100% accuracy. What kind of data would we retrieve?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What is this app for?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This app is primarily for entertainment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The important thing is that this hasn&amp;#39;t been done before, and the data hasn&amp;#39;t been created, before.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With hundreds of thousands of 93% to 97% accurate poll answers, we can just find cool and interesting things about cities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The image below illustrates the concept. I will create a video later on.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/05zylvpz2bw71.png?width=3058&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=2c6946bc09df8e4f8f195845c509138507a19dbe&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/05zylvpz2bw71.png?width=3058&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=2c6946bc09df8e4f8f195845c509138507a19dbe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Automatic Windows configuration with Ansible]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hi!

Recently I was migrating one of my home machines to the new Windows 11. In the
process of reinstalling, I decided it was time to automate the configuration and
created an ansible playbook that does most of the work of preparing the system
for software development.

Current Capabilities:

 *…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qichs3/automatic_windows_configuration_with_ansible/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qichs3/automatic_windows_configuration_with_ansible/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 14:33:06 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Recently I was migrating one of my home machines to the new Windows 11. In the process of reinstalling, I decided it was time to automate the configuration and created an ansible playbook that does most of the work of preparing the system for software development.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Current Capabilities:  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Software&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensures Bloatware removed (see default config for a complete list of Bloatware).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure software and packages selected by the user are installed via Chocolatey.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Windows apps &amp;amp; features&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensures the Optional Windows Features selected by the user are installed and enabled.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensures WSL2 distro selected by the user is installed and enabled.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Windows Settings&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Explorer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensures Explorer includes the file extension in file names.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensures Explorer opens itself to the Computer view.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensures Ribbon menu is disabled in Windows Explorer.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensures Right-click Context Menu enabled (Windows 11).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Start Menu&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensures Automatic Install of Suggested Apps disabled.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensures App Suggestions in Start menu disabled.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensures popup &amp;quot;tips&amp;quot; about Windows disabled.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensures &amp;#39;Windows Welcome Experience&amp;#39; disabled.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Taskbar&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensures &amp;#39;Search&amp;#39; unpinned from Taskbar.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensures Task View, Chat and Cortana are unpinned from Taskbar.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensures &amp;#39;News and Interests&amp;#39; unpinned from Taskbar.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensures &amp;#39;People&amp;#39; unpinned from Taskbar.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensures &amp;#39;Edge&amp;#39;, &amp;#39;Store&amp;#39; other built-in shortcuts unpinned from Taskbar.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Desktop&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure Desktop icons are removed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensures mouse acceleration is disabled.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure sound scheme set to &amp;#39;No sounds&amp;#39;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure the power plan selected by the user is set.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure Windows updates are selected by the user installed.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure configured hostname selected by the user is set.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are still many things that I  want to add, such as startup menu and taskbar icons automatic pin/unpin,  but at this point, it already does a  pretty good job and it also works well with Windows 10.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested and want to use something similar on your home machine, you can check out my repo here:  &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/AlexNabokikh/windows-playbook&quot;&gt;https://github.com/AlexNabokikh/windows-playbook&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tips and criticism are welcome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Many thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Made a website for remote jobs and remote work stories]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qi74e8/made_a_website_for_remote_jobs_and_remote_work/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qi74e8/made_a_website_for_remote_jobs_and_remote_work/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 13:31:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I am building SaaS to help to monetize your APIs]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qho77a/i_am_building_saas_to_help_to_monetize_your_apis/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qho77a/i_am_building_saas_to_help_to_monetize_your_apis/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 20:51:52 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How to launch on Product Hunt, a detailed Guide]]></title><description><![CDATA[Product Hunt is probably the most knowledgeable and visited website in the
startup ecosystem. All founders, entrepreneurs, VC keep an eye on it to see what
are the new trends. So, having a product that hits the top #5 of the day will
bring you thousands of visits, some attention from all over the…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qhpjau/how_to_launch_on_product_hunt_a_detailed_guide/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qhpjau/how_to_launch_on_product_hunt_a_detailed_guide/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 18:28:09 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Product  Hunt is probably the most knowledgeable and visited website in the startup ecosystem. All founders, entrepreneurs, VC keep an eye on it to see what are the new trends. So, having a product that hits the top #5  of the day will bring you thousands of visits, some attention from all over the world, and even some PR. Product Hunt is THE place to get your early traction. Here is a guide of how to get more out of your launch. &lt;em&gt;It is an extract of&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://userbooster.co/&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;UserBooster&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;, a Notion Dashboard that helps you get your first users and build your launch strategy.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;When to launch on PH&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bad news about Product hunt is: you only have one shot. You can’t post the same product twice, except if you made some major upgrade. So you better get a good launch! That’s why I don’t advise you to launch fast on PH. My advice here is to wait until you get your first feedback and a  small audience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Build Followers&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First,  build an audience (use the other acquisition channel on this dashboard to do it). You will need a couple of hundreds of upvotes to hit the front page, so grow a mailing list of at least 500+ followers (or any other sort of audience, like Twitter). If you start from scratch, I  highly recommend using the “Ship” feature of ProductHunt. Creating a  following base directly on PH is much more actionable when you launch!  In the meantime, start some conversation in the Discussion section of  PH. As always, try to bring value to your topic. It should give you some followers as well. Connect all your social media to PH. That way, all your Twitter, FB friends will see your PH profile and will follow you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Build a good product&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That sounds obvious, but if you want to get all these upvotes, you better have a good product!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Iterate on your product as much as you can. Use the feedback you got from your early users to build the “perfect” product.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Work on the UI/UX. You’ll be spawned in a list with plenty of other projects. You better stand out!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create some growth/retention strategy. You will have tons of visits during the launch day. Be sure to have a way to transform all this traffic into conversion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You’ll receive a massive spike of traffic on launch day, so be prepared!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Get some testimonials/social proof before launch. That will help for conversion!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;How to postTiming&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;1.1 Hours&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Product  Hunt launches are all about timing! The homepage is reset every day at  12 am PST. So schedule your post just after 12 am PST, that way, you’ll have 24hrs of exposure. It’s also a good way to get some traction before the big guys from Silicon Valley! When scheduling your post, set the time zone to PST. Product Hunt does not adjust for different time zones.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;1.2 Days&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want maximum exposure and traffic, you should launch on  Tuesday/Wednesday/Thursday. They also are the most competitive days -  launch there only if you’re fully prepared! Tip: use weekends for your  small projects, you’ll get less traffic, but your chance to be ranked  are better&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Catchy listing&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;1.1 Title&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This one is easy. Just use the name of your product, no emojis&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;1.2 Logo &amp;amp; tagline&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The  logo is a 240x240 image, and that’s what attracts visitors! Use a  high-contrast logo to stand out easily. Don’t overthink it. Use Canva  and make a simple one. The GIF is not really a thing nowadays, as they  don’t auto-play. The tagline is also essential. Create several versions.  Pick the more impactful&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;1.3 Slides or Video&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Two missions here:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Tell the world your product’s purpose&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Show your product and convince visitors that they want to know more (and upvote/comment)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You  should really spend some time on the slide, not really on the design  (again, use Canva), but on the content. Explain what problem you’re  solving and how it will help your customers be faster/cheaper/… If  you’re comfortable with video, do it, I really think it is worth it.  Loom is probably the best way to go here. Create a short screencast to  show your solution&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;1.4 Maker’s comment&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Your first comment as a maker is super important. It should contain&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What’s the problem you’re solving&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;How you’re solving it&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Who  can benefit from it Try to add something that leads to engagement on  your comment, like a question. The more comment you’ll get, the more  product hunt will promote you.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;1.5 Discount (optional)&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s  not mandatory, but the ProductHunt community appreciates it when you  create a special discount for the launch. I personally created a 20%  discount for 48hrs after the launch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Launch Day&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first hours are crucial. The US is still sleeping. That’s when you need to stand out quickly!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GOAL: hit the homepage asap&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To do that, you’ll need as many upvotes/comments as you can in the first 3-4 hours!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contact all your UE/Asian-based contacts and share your launch!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Post on FB groups, Slack channels, etc&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Post here as well!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Interact as much as you can!&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Answer  to EVERY comment on product hunt and on every platform you posted on,  every DM you have as fast as you can. Start discussions! I got 80+  comments on UserBooster launch, which clearly helped me to rank faster.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Don’t be spammy!&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People  will support you when you launch, don’t spam people asking for upvotes.  Don’t ask people to create new accounts, or your product can be banned!  Try to get some real engagement instead, answer questions, start  conversations. If you’re not on the homepage after an hour (despite  having more upvotes/comments than your competitors), contact the PH team  on Twitter! It happened to me, UserBooster was stuck in the “New”  section. I messaged ProductHunt and they fixed the issue within 10  minutes!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt; After the Launch&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A  launch on product Hunt will bring you some traffic for at least a week  after the D-Day! You’ll receive some comments on your page, some  questions on social media, a lot of new connections as well - and maybe  some PR requests.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Don’t forget to answer them!&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And use this launch to grow your audience and reputation online!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Share your experience/insights/results with your audience&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Look for PH collections website, ask for an update&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Put a nice PH badge on your website&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Bonus point: the PH newsletters&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re ranked enough, your product will be in the Daily and weekly newsletter. Each newsletter brought me 1000+ visitors!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;Conclusion&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now  you know everything about launching on Product Hunt. I used these  techniques to launch my products, that’s I managed to be ranked in the  top products on the day! I hope you the best for your launches! 🚀🚀 If  you have any questions or suggestions, I’d be happy to talk to you about  Product Hunt, your launch, or anything else.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Contact me on Twitter: &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/angezanetti&quot;&gt;https://twitter.com/angezanetti&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I created a free, automated newsletter that summarizes recent investments by leadings VCs]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qhk2i5/i_created_a_free_automated_newsletter_that/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qhk2i5/i_created_a_free_automated_newsletter_that/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 17:09:17 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Help me pick my next thumbnail. Vote in comments please.]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qhjlz9/help_me_pick_my_next_thumbnail_vote_in_comments/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qhjlz9/help_me_pick_my_next_thumbnail_vote_in_comments/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 14:22:46 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[My Notion to Help Center/Documentation tool just reached $100 MRR. Here are my three lessons so far...]]></title><description><![CDATA[After almost two months since launching on Twitter, my SaaS HelpKit
[https://www.helpkit.so/] just reached $100 MRR ($122 to be precise) which is a
big milestone for me a solo bootstrapped founder.

There are now 3 customers on the Premium Plan for $29/month and 2 customers on
the Essential Plan for…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qhlosl/my_notion_to_help_centerdocumentation_tool_just/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qhlosl/my_notion_to_help_centerdocumentation_tool_just/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 13:47:33 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;After almost two months since launching on Twitter, my SaaS &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.helpkit.so/&quot;&gt;HelpKit&lt;/a&gt; just reached $100 MRR (&lt;em&gt;$122 to be precise&lt;/em&gt;) which is a big milestone for me a solo bootstrapped founder.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are now 3 customers on the Premium Plan for $29/month and 2 customers on the Essential Plan for $19/month. Excluding the two pre-order customers that paid $40 for a full year of HelpKit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In terms of marketing, I would say &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/sobedominik/status/1451624399208005633&quot;&gt;building in public on Twitter&lt;/a&gt; is helping me the most. Additionally, I also did two little growth hacks that have seemed to have helped. You can read about them here in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.indiehackers.com/post/first-customers-rolling-in-and-early-marketing-efforts-slowly-showing-results-655186902d&quot;&gt;this post&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since everything is super early, unfortunately I don&amp;#39;t have too much advice for you at this stage. That said, here are the &lt;strong&gt;three things I learned&lt;/strong&gt; so far:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1)&lt;/strong&gt; 👋Show up up every day and engage with your potential customers as best as you can. Yesterday someone wrote me: &amp;quot;Thanks and really appreciate the personalised support!&amp;quot; That&amp;#39;s what you want to receive. If possible try to answer in a matter of hours and not the next day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2)&lt;/strong&gt; 🙅🏽‍♂️Don&amp;#39;t bend your product or price too much in the beginning unless 99% of your requests are to do so. I have received a couple of emails telling me they would signup if the product would do X or decrease the price because of Y. If the requests are not part of your roadmap, it&amp;#39;s better to just kindly tell them that. If they value what you do, they will sign up. If not, they won&amp;#39;t. There are so many things to do and bending yourself just for this one potential customer is not worth it. A funny side note; One of these potential customers subscribed to the Premium plan and replied to my email with: &amp;quot;Thanks - that&amp;#39;s very helpful and appreciate the honesty!&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3)&lt;/strong&gt; 🚀Build in public. BIP de-risks you on a personal level, people trust you and your product more and might also be more forgiving if you make some errors.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m excited for this journey and feel like this is just the start 🙂&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me know if you have any questions! Happy to answer.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Made a game where you guess prices from Amazon.com (try to beat 5!)]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qhbgmc/made_a_game_where_you_guess_prices_from_amazoncom/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qhbgmc/made_a_game_where_you_guess_prices_from_amazoncom/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 10:50:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Just added these thread generating features to my product before I launch]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qhh7m8/just_added_these_thread_generating_features_to_my/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qhh7m8/just_added_these_thread_generating_features_to_my/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 08:47:08 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I built a website for browsing UI references for web apps]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qh4ps8/i_built_a_website_for_browsing_ui_references_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qh4ps8/i_built_a_website_for_browsing_ui_references_for/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 03:15:15 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How I failed 5 side projects in 6 years, earning $0]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qh804c/how_i_failed_5_side_projects_in_6_years_earning_0/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qh804c/how_i_failed_5_side_projects_in_6_years_earning_0/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 02:36:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[We are live on Product Hunt today! Currently in 15th Place 🚀🚀🚀]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hi everyone! After many cups of coffee and many more hours of hard work, my
co-founder and I launched our free coding font tool! It is a fun mini tool to
help select a font for your coding editor through an exciting tournament-style
game! ⚔️ (Squid Games, anyone?)

Why we did it
We are both…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qh36ej/we_are_live_on_product_hunt_today_currently_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qh36ej/we_are_live_on_product_hunt_today_currently_in/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 23:26:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi everyone! After many cups of coffee and many more hours of hard work, my co-founder and I launched our free coding font tool! It is a fun mini tool to help select a font for your coding editor through an exciting tournament-style game! ⚔️ (Squid Games, anyone?)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why we did it&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
We are both passionate about design and fonts. Also, this is personal: As devs, we spend a lot of time staring at our screen coding. The coding font that we spend 8 hours a day staring at affects our productivity and comfort. I&amp;#39;m picky about coding fonts and like to experiment with settings to find the optimal balance. This is especially true for coding fonts, as they inherently share mono-spaced characteristics. To solve this, I thought: How about looking at two fonts at a time and picking the better one, rinse and repeat in a tournament style until you have the winner? That way, you&amp;#39;ll have some fun and find the perfect font.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What the tool does&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
Choose your favorite coding fonts and pit them against each other Eliminate font one by one to get your ideal font Tournament map of all the fonts you have picked&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope this unique app experience makes your time worthwhile and allows you to find the most pleasing yet comforting font that will skyrocket your productivity. You can check it out on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.producthunt.com/posts/coding-font&quot;&gt;PH here&lt;/a&gt; and leave us some feedback if you feel like. Thank you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[How we made it to #4 Product of the day on Product Hunt. Our story, learnings and tips.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hey!

On 15th October 2021 me and my friend launched on ProductHunt for the first
time. I decided to share an aftermath of BlogAudio [https://blogaudio.co/]’s
launch. I really hope that some of you will find it helpful.

It’s a bit lengthy so feel free to skip to the part that you find…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qgv0lh/how_we_made_it_to_4_product_of_the_day_on_product/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qgv0lh/how_we_made_it_to_4_product_of_the_day_on_product/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 22:19:47 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On 15th October 2021 me and my friend launched on ProductHunt for the first time. I decided to share an aftermath of &lt;a href=&quot;https://blogaudio.co/&quot;&gt;BlogAudio&lt;/a&gt;’s launch. I really hope that some of you will find it helpful.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s a bit lengthy so feel free to skip to the part that you find most interesting. There’s also a little bonus at the end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;1. Our first launch was a total failure&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We wanted to launch on ProductHunt for quite some time and we always felt unprepared so we started postponing the scheduled launch. &lt;a href=&quot;https://blogaudio.co/&quot;&gt;BlogAudio&lt;/a&gt; was also listed on AppSumo and we wanted to take it down before the launch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We finally decided to launch on Tuesday (12th October) and I re-scheduled the launch for that day. At least I thought I did. On Friday (8th October) I got an email from a guy named Jesus (if you’re reading it, thanks again) saying he upvoted &lt;a href=&quot;https://blogaudio.co/&quot;&gt;BlogAudio&lt;/a&gt; on ProductHunt. I was a bit shocked but I checked ProductHunt and there it was. &lt;a href=&quot;https://blogaudio.co/&quot;&gt;BlogAudio&lt;/a&gt; launched without us knowing it, got 8 upvotes and was under the “view all products” fold. It was already 9 hours into the launch day so it was basically game over.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I used the chat available on ProductHunt’s website to contact them and they replied incredibly fast. I explained the situation and they helped by putting the product down and allowing us to launch one more time — this time intentionally. Huge thanks to ProductHunt team here! That’s the customer support we all need.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;2. Preparation for “the real” launch&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We prepared all needed assets and a to-do list for the launch day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Assets:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Made good profile pictures and uploaded them. I think it’s important to see who stands behind the product.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Wrote all texts recommended by ProductHunt, including the first comment. &lt;strong&gt;Tip:&lt;/strong&gt; upvote that first comment so it stays on top.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepared a gif for &lt;a href=&quot;https://blogaudio.co/&quot;&gt;BlogAudio&lt;/a&gt;. We read that it’s no longer a thing but we decided to do it anyways.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepared a post for IndieHackers which explained that we are live on PH and they can check us out.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepared good graphics that show our product.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Asked our closest ones for support on PH that day.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Prepared email to our current customers to let them know we are live on PH.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Just to clarify, we did not ask for upvotes, comments or reviews. Just informed that we are live on PH, hoping that people will check us out and support the launch.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our to-do list for the launch day:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Embed a ProductHunt launch badge&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ask our closest ones for support&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Post on IndieHackers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Send email to current customers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Post on HackerNews: Show HN&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Post on Twitter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Post on Entre&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;3. Launch day&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the launch day we were sitting in front of our computers 20 minutes before the launch. We scheduled it for 12:01 a.m. PST. For us this was good because it was 9:01 a.m. in our time zone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The goal was to be as close to the top as possible in the first hour. This first hour really seems to be crucial. We did most of the things from our to-do-list in the first 20 minutes or so and managed to stay in top 3 during that time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Later during the day we had some ups and downs as we were as low as #5, but not lower. I was answering each comment as soon as possible. We’ve also posted in some subreddits. Again, these posts were informational (e.g. we are live on PH, we are #4 so far. Check us out if you’re interested). My co-founder stayed up until late at night to keep an eye on the launch and I got up at 7 a.m. (2 hours before the launch day ended) to answer some comments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Eventually we ended up being &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.producthunt.com/posts/blogaudio-2&quot;&gt;#4 Product of the Day&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;4. What worked and what didn’t work for us&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What worked:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We were well-prepared and very quick with our actions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We made the most out of the first hour&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My post on IndieHackers got quite popular. I don’t know how many of those who saw it actually supported the launch but even if it was 5 or 10 people, it was worth it.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I got 2 or 3 email replies from our customers saying they supported the launch&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Friday is not as competitive as Tuesday, Wednesday or Thursday so it might have helped&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other than that, I believe people actually liked &lt;a href=&quot;https://blogaudio.co/&quot;&gt;BlogAudio&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What didn’t work:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Twitter. We don’t have any followers on our private accounts and &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/blogaudio_&quot;&gt;official BlogAudio’s account&lt;/a&gt; had 17 followers when we launched. Probably that’s the reason why posting there didn’t help us.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Post on HackerNews. Maybe it was the wrong time of the day but we didn’t get much traffic from there. We showed our main page and hoped that visitors will notice the ProductHunt badge and support the launch.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Post on Entre. I gave it a shot but it didn’t help much.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Learnings&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Having some kind of community such as IndieHackers/Twitter/ProductHunt followers can make a huge difference.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Being well-prepared and organized is very important for the launch day.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;We should probably be more specific with our requests in posts and emails. We didn’t ask for upvotes or comments in order not to violate the rules but we should have asked for support.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Having a famous hunter may help significantly but it is not necessary. It’s all about community again. If someone who is followed by 8,000 people on PH hunts a product, those people get email notifications. It’s quite obvious that it will positively impact that product’s performance.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Having more upvotes, comments or even reviews doesn’t necessarily mean that your product will rank higher. It was a surprise to me to be honest but that’s the fact. There have to be many more factors than this but we didn’t figure them out yet. We suspect that the following may play a role: the pace at which a product gets upvotes, number of product views and clicks, reputation of hunters that comment and upvote a product.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
We are happy with the result. Since the launch we got 97 signups and more than 1,100 visits. We also got some interesting business proposals so the launch was worth all the effort.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our next big challange is to convert those who signed up to our paying customers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1&gt;5. Our next product&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One last thing. At the beginning of November we are launching &lt;a href=&quot;https://raport.pro/&quot;&gt;Raport&lt;/a&gt;. It’s an all-in-one analytics tool that allows you to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Connect metrics from multiple data sources. For example: revenue from Stripe and Shopify or page views from Google Analytics.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Analyze all your data in one app. It is aggregated by metric, synchronized and displayed in one dashboard.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Receive daily, weekly and monthly reports by email or Slack. Set up custom alerts to get notified about changes in your metrics as soon as they occur.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’d like to give it a try &lt;a href=&quot;https://raport.pro/&quot;&gt;sign up for a waiting list to get FREE access to beta&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[One shopping cart to rule them all, access anywhere and checkout everywhere. Nevrfull.com]]></title><description><![CDATA[Universal shopping cart with one click checkout that lets users save for later,
build lists, share and checkout easily. Built to combat cart abandonment and to
make consumers lives easier. Beta en route.

Feedback needed and appreciated. Checkout the overview vid tis short :) and
sign-up for early…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qgu9qa/one_shopping_cart_to_rule_them_all_access/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qgu9qa/one_shopping_cart_to_rule_them_all_access/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 18:31:16 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Universal shopping cart with one click checkout that lets users save for later, build lists, share and checkout easily. Built to combat cart abandonment and to make consumers lives easier. Beta en route.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Feedback needed and appreciated. Checkout the overview vid tis short :) and sign-up for early access&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://reddit.com/link/qgu9qa/video/b80ada7s7zv71/player&quot;&gt;https://reddit.com/link/qgu9qa/video/b80ada7s7zv71/player&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Keyboard shortcuts interface for your website]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qh0msj/keyboard_shortcuts_interface_for_your_website/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qh0msj/keyboard_shortcuts_interface_for_your_website/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 17:36:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Made an NFT gallery app that runs seamlessly on all Apple devices from Watch to TV]]></title><description><![CDATA[I've built an app [https://apps.apple.com/us/app/nft-art-gallery/id1585837631]
for NFT lovers to discover and browse artwork in one seamless experience on all
their Apple devices from Watch to TV:

 * Explore top-selling and top-traded NFTs on OpenSea (more platforms to be
   added soon)
 * Display…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qgbype/made_an_nft_gallery_app_that_runs_seamlessly_on/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qgbype/made_an_nft_gallery_app_that_runs_seamlessly_on/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 16:07:12 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve built an &lt;a href=&quot;https://apps.apple.com/us/app/nft-art-gallery/id1585837631&quot;&gt;app&lt;/a&gt; for NFT lovers to discover and browse artwork in one seamless experience on all their Apple devices from Watch to TV:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Explore top-selling and top-traded NFTs on OpenSea (more platforms to be added soon)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Display NFTs by Ethereum wallet address&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Flip through items or start a slideshow&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Save favorites that sync automatically&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://apps.apple.com/us/app/nft-art-gallery/id1585837631&quot;&gt;app&lt;/a&gt; is still pretty basic, what features would you love to see added next?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/kjmye1um1uv71.png?width=1920&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=c2502844a1e8fdddef8ea75159569365345f22fb&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/kjmye1um1uv71.png?width=1920&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=c2502844a1e8fdddef8ea75159569365345f22fb&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I'm making BotMeNot - a tool that tests websites' bot protection level]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hello, r/SideProject [/r/SideProject]

After working on multiple eCommerce-related projects, I've now decided to
develop BotMeNot [https://botmenot.com/] - a SaaS that tests websites' bot
protection levels.

It has been in the making for some time now, but there's still a couple of more
things that…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qgwt9q/im_making_botmenot_a_tool_that_tests_websites_bot/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qgwt9q/im_making_botmenot_a_tool_that_tests_websites_bot/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 15:32:25 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello, &lt;a href=&quot;/r/SideProject&quot;&gt;r/SideProject&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After working on multiple eCommerce-related projects, I&amp;#39;ve now decided to develop &lt;a href=&quot;https://botmenot.com/&quot;&gt;BotMeNot&lt;/a&gt; - a SaaS that tests websites&amp;#39; bot protection levels.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has been in the making for some time now, but there&amp;#39;s still a couple of more things that need to be done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main idea behind it is to let its users know how well protected a certain website is against malicious bot activity. You can think of it as a diagnostic tool. It can give you a better insight into how effective your existing bot protection solution is or if you&amp;#39;re looking for a solution where you currently stand and what you may need the most.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The main deliverable is going to be the score itself and the evidence of the testing done (screenshots, data gathered, and the list of requests and outcomes).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me know what you think and could it be useful to you!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I'm a VLC dev and made MotionMonkey 1.3.0 🐵 , a streamlined Web + BitTorrent player based on OpenSource technologies. Just added live feeds and Chromecast support 📺. Available on the PlayStore.]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qgvxy2/im_a_vlc_dev_and_made_motionmonkey_130_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qgvxy2/im_a_vlc_dev_and_made_motionmonkey_130_a/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 14:23:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Open-source is eating the world: Ex-Firebase investor co-leads a $10m seed round for the open-source alternative]]></title><description><![CDATA[Appwrite started out as our side project over a year back and we're super
thrilled on reaching this exciting milestone.

Appwrite is an open-source, self-hosted alternative to Firebase that provides
developers with all the core APIs and services required to build any kind of
modern software no…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qgqqib/opensource_is_eating_the_world_exfirebase/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qgqqib/opensource_is_eating_the_world_exfirebase/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 09:24:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Appwrite started out as our side project over a year back and we&amp;#39;re super thrilled on reaching this exciting milestone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Appwrite is an open-source, self-hosted alternative to Firebase that provides developers with all the core APIs and services required to build any kind of modern software no matter the platform. Appwrite aims to make software development fast, simple and most importantly, enjoyable. Appwrite integrates with Web, Android iOS, Flutter and any server-side language.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In essence, Appwrite takes care of all the things you would typically need to build from scratch, saving you the complexity and time to focus on your application. In essence&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can ready more about our recent funding round here &lt;a href=&quot;https://hazardlights.net/2021/10/26/our-investment-in-appwrite/&quot;&gt;https://hazardlights.net/2021/10/26/our-investment-in-appwrite/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We would be more than happy to share our learning with all of you. We&amp;#39;ll be here in the comments if you need anything.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Denigma is an AI that reads and explains code in understandable English and documents codebases.]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://denigma.app
[https://denigma.app/?fbclid=IwAR2J4tBQkKp9IS_JiWo4VTyj5gJMqOWbBKT6NQuLyGcm0s5zMcOthN8Bseg] is
an AI that reads and explains code in understandable English and documents
codebases. In a few days, we're launching with:

 * A VS Code extension 
 * The ability to explain files on…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qgeugu/denigma_is_an_ai_that_reads_and_explains_code_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qgeugu/denigma_is_an_ai_that_reads_and_explains_code_in/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 04:54:59 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://denigma.app/?fbclid=IwAR2J4tBQkKp9IS_JiWo4VTyj5gJMqOWbBKT6NQuLyGcm0s5zMcOthN8Bseg&quot;&gt;https://denigma.app&lt;/a&gt; is an AI that reads and explains code in understandable English and documents codebases. In a few days, we&amp;#39;re launching with:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;A VS Code extension &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The ability to explain files on GitHub through a chrome extension&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Denigma search - AI code search engine where you can describe the code you’re searching for and get instant results. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;(@DenigmaAI) TWEET US your feedback! We&amp;#39;re currently building and we value feedback and ideas from our target audience! Be sure to join the waitlist if you like it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Be sure to test your most complex code on &lt;a href=&quot;https://denigma.app/?fbclid=IwAR0Ik_AkprPadEYrqxYe9pp0O5XkjRpE1l1fVUHM-Ui2GqwtKmBL33Ms9WY&quot;&gt;https://denigma.app&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I created a tool to schedule HTTP requests]]></title><description><![CDATA[In my last project, I was struggling to create and monitor cron jobs.

So, instead of creating hundreds of standalone scrips and executing them with
cron, I decided to turn those scripts into multiple endpoints. Next, I created a
single service that I could schedule HTTP requests to those endpoints…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qgcifx/i_created_a_tool_to_schedule_http_requests/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qgcifx/i_created_a_tool_to_schedule_http_requests/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 02:38:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;In my last project, I was struggling to create and monitor cron jobs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, instead of creating hundreds of standalone scrips and executing them with cron, I decided to turn those scripts into multiple endpoints. Next, I created a single service that I could schedule HTTP requests to those endpoints and monitor its execution. No more scripts, now everything is endpoints that I can run manually at any time  😊&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I turned this scheduler service into a Micro-SaaS so you don&amp;#39;t have to build it yourself: &lt;a href=&quot;http://beew.io/&quot;&gt;beew.io&lt;/a&gt; 🎉&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;btw, feedbacks are welcome. 😃&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[A personal assistant bot in Telegram]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hey guys,

I'm developing a personal assistant bot for telegram. I just made version 0.1
public. If you want to give it a shot you can read more about it at
https://ambrosio.nunodonato.com/ and see the current features it supports.

More on the way, and would love your feedback and suggestions on…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qgf90g/a_personal_assistant_bot_in_telegram/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qgf90g/a_personal_assistant_bot_in_telegram/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 21:48:44 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey guys,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m  developing a personal assistant bot for telegram. I just made version  0.1 public. If you want to give it a shot you can read more about it at &lt;a href=&quot;https://ambrosio.nunodonato.com/&quot;&gt;https://ambrosio.nunodonato.com/&lt;/a&gt; and see the current features it supports.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More on the way, and would love your feedback and suggestions on how to make it useful :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;thanks in advance&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Looking to support some projects that have monthly subscriptions..]]></title><description><![CDATA[It’s a little difficult to sort projects people are working on vs ones that are
ready to be used by the public (even if some features are missing)

I’m looking to sign up for some projects that are ready to be used (or almost
ready..) and could use a little motivation by having someone sign…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qg4gol/looking_to_support_some_projects_that_have/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qg4gol/looking_to_support_some_projects_that_have/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 20:48:04 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s a little difficult to sort projects people are working on vs ones that are ready to be used by the public (even if some features are missing) &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m looking to sign up for some projects that are ready to be used (or almost ready..) and could use a little motivation by having someone sign up. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please drop a link to your site!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Worst House on the Internet]]></title><description><![CDATA[Remember when you went trick-or-treating and there was always that one house on
the block that gave out the worst treats? Now everyone on the Internet can
re-experience that same feeling of Halloween disappointment. You’re welcome!

www.theworsthouseontheinternet.com…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qfu56w/the_worst_house_on_the_internet/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qfu56w/the_worst_house_on_the_internet/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 20:35:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Remember when you went trick-or-treating and there was always that one house on the block that gave out the worst treats? Now everyone on the Internet can re-experience that same feeling of Halloween disappointment. You’re welcome!  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theworsthouseontheinternet.com&quot;&gt;www.theworsthouseontheinternet.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/4erv9k1ysov71.png?width=1270&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=9ad5d638299e6f84dc3e569302b7743563585309&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/4erv9k1ysov71.png?width=1270&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=9ad5d638299e6f84dc3e569302b7743563585309&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Made a website listing jobs with a 4 day work week]]></title><description><![CDATA[I started building this at the start of the year and recently hit 50 tech
companies which have a 4 day work week (i.e. 32 hours per week with no drop in
pay)

Jobs are updated daily:http://4dayweek.io/

Hope you like and all feedback welcome :)]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qg3nyq/made_a_website_listing_jobs_with_a_4_day_work_week/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qg3nyq/made_a_website_listing_jobs_with_a_4_day_work_week/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 11:33:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I started building this at the start of the year and recently hit 50 tech companies which have a 4 day work week (i.e. 32 hours per week with no drop in pay)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jobs are updated daily:&lt;a href=&quot;http://4dayweek.io/&quot;&gt;http://4dayweek.io/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hope you like and all feedback welcome :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Add dark mode on your website within 3 mins]]></title><description><![CDATA[Heyy r/SideProject [/r/SideProject]!!

Made a simple application to add dark mode on any website - https://darkmode.to/

Please let me know what you think.

 * Once you add your domain, it'll fetch all the colors from your website and
   auto-generate the dark mode colors. You'll get a small snippet…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qg24c9/add_dark_mode_on_your_website_within_3_mins/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qg24c9/add_dark_mode_on_your_website_within_3_mins/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 10:33:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Heyy &lt;a href=&quot;/r/SideProject&quot;&gt;r/SideProject&lt;/a&gt;!!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Made a simple application to add dark mode on any website - &lt;a href=&quot;https://darkmode.to/&quot;&gt;https://darkmode.to/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please let me know what you think.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Once you add your domain, it&amp;#39;ll fetch all the colors from your website and auto-generate the dark mode colors. You&amp;#39;ll get a small snippet to add to your website.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can tweak the colors if you wish. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You can upload images to swap against the ones in white mode. For ex. some pictures with white backgrounds won&amp;#39;t look good on dark mode.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ll be adding features to auto-detect user&amp;#39;s default OS settings&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you&amp;#39;d like to give it a spin, please feel free to DM me or signup on the website. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/46kl9rkbcrv71.png?width=1217&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=d352749cfc07b5ff98406e5c49c405b7df885cfb&quot;&gt;darkmode.to in white mode&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/n4ggcqkbcrv71.png?width=1212&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=0301335655e6ecbfe78d9e336ce1235f94124cf7&quot;&gt;dogfooding my own product&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Form Builder for Google Sheets]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qfizj6/form_builder_for_google_sheets/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qfizj6/form_builder_for_google_sheets/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 05:21:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[A good read if you're looking for some extra motivation for those creative side projects! DIFY]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qfhr2p/a_good_read_if_youre_looking_for_some_extra/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qfhr2p/a_good_read_if_youre_looking_for_some_extra/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 04:19:32 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Update on my Space industry job board! ( link in comments )]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qfoap7/update_on_my_space_industry_job_board_link_in/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qfoap7/update_on_my_space_industry_job_board_link_in/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 26 Oct 2021 00:44:30 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[My little website builder allows you copy-paste your Spotify podcast in every text field. Try it free at https://pazly.dev/]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qfkbpz/my_little_website_builder_allows_you_copypaste/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qfkbpz/my_little_website_builder_allows_you_copypaste/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 22:17:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[We made a stock scanner / screener web app for day traders. Available with a free plan.]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qfnlim/we_made_a_stock_scanner_screener_web_app_for_day/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qfnlim/we_made_a_stock_scanner_screener_web_app_for_day/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 20:23:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Created this app where people can anonymously start discussions on any topic. Link to site in comments]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qfj4gj/created_this_app_where_people_can_anonymously/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/qfj4gj/created_this_app_where_people_can_anonymously/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 19:44:49 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>