<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[业余项目分享交流]]></title><description><![CDATA[用中文浏览reddit业余项目讨论]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc</link><generator>GatsbyJS</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Sep 2021 04:33:34 GMT</lastBuildDate><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><item><title><![CDATA[Proud to present you Fakeflix, a Netflix Clone built with React, Redux, Firebase & Framer Motion]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/ob5lsy/proud_to_present_you_fakeflix_a_netflix_clone/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/ob5lsy/proud_to_present_you_fakeflix_a_netflix_clone/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 22:26:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I taught myself how to code so I could build a phone contract comparison website. Any feedback will really be appreciated!]]></title><description><![CDATA[TL;DR: Learnt to code and built CompareDial [https://www.comparedial.com]

When I was younger I used to build simple websites with Geocities and Microsoft
Frontpage. I was more focused with the design aspect of websites rather than
actual programming - not because I had no interest in programming,…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/oayq7x/i_taught_myself_how_to_code_so_i_could_build_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/oayq7x/i_taught_myself_how_to_code_so_i_could_build_a/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 18:01:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;TL;DR: Learnt to code and built &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.comparedial.com&quot;&gt;CompareDial&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I was younger I used to build simple websites with Geocities and Microsoft Frontpage. I was more focused with the design aspect of websites rather than actual programming - not because I had no interest in programming, but rather because I found it intimidating. I was scared to even start. I eventually started to design websites in Photoshop and slice them with some basic HTML and CSS knowledge, but would progress no further. I simply enjoyed designing and would do it for fun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I had an idea for a phone and SIM contract comparison website, where users could search from thousands of deals and filter down to their specific needs. There were already a few out there, but I found a lot of them lacking in features, generally low in quality and would promote specific deals that would earn them more commission rather than showing the cheapest possible deals. How hard could it be, right? Boy was I wrong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My idea was to design the website and hire someone to make it. I made notes, drew sketches and obsessed over how the site would work. I have a tendency to over design and obsess over minor details, to a point where it holds me back. Everything had to work, behave and be constructed in a very specific way. If I hired someone to make my product and it wasn’t up to my exact standards, I wouldn’t progress with it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I quickly realised that I wouldn’t be able to get my product made up to my standard unless I was willing to spend A LOT of money. Even then, I still probably wouldn’t be satisfied. The only other logical solution was to learn how to program and make it myself, which is exactly what I did.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I did some research and landed on JavaScript as the ideal language for me to learn and build my product, as I could use my skills on the front end and back end. I followed every basic JavaScript tutorial and eventually landed on &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/getify/You-Dont-Know-JS&quot;&gt;You Don’t Know Js&lt;/a&gt; - an absolute must read, even for experienced JS developers. I tried to pick up on my basic HTML and CSS skills from years ago, but I found myself starting from scratch. ‘Flexbox? Grids? What the hell is any of this?!?” - I used to use tables back in my day! I also followed some online tutorials for basic SQL, realising I would need a database of some sort to store all the deals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started to feel a bit more confident, even though I hadn’t even begun to build. Eventually, after hours of pulling my hair out, I somehow pulled together a simple prototype that just about worked. It was rubbish, but I thought it was the best thing ever at the time. I couldn’t even imagine I would be able to progress past simple JS a few months prior, but here I was, with something I could be proud of.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a perfectionist, in the coming months I must have started over from scratch hundreds of times. I wasn’t happy. Eventually, I convinced myself to plan on launching. I started to add more retailers and feeds to my website, but I hit a bottleneck - the website became mind bogglingly slow. I was building my product around one or two retailers with no more than 1,000 deals. But now, I had over 200,000 deals, and everything grinded to a halt. A simple request would take up to 10 seconds. How could I be so stupid? I tried optimising my SQL, learning about database indexes, but with no avail. I was tempted to throw in the towel, but somehow persisted, eventually learning about caching and indexing. I ended up adding Redis and Meilisearch to the stack. It was a blessing in disguise as I learnt so much about how to architect such a product for performance - something that I wouldn’t have learnt if I did not run into this bottleneck.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are some technologies I’ve learnt along the way, all within a few hours of work a few week in just under 2 years.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;JavaScript&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Node&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Nginx&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Linux&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Redis&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Meilisearch&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SQL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Postgres&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Git &amp;amp; GitHub&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Bash&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And finally, my launched product:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.comparedial.com&quot;&gt;CompareDial&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[We've built a tool to turn hardcoded strings into editable content]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://dico.app

18 seconds demo [https://reddit.com/link/oaxk6z/video/2nk1k6yfqe871/player]]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/oaxk6z/weve_built_a_tool_to_turn_hardcoded_strings_into/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/oaxk6z/weve_built_a_tool_to_turn_hardcoded_strings_into/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 15:52:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://dico.app&quot;&gt;https://dico.app&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://reddit.com/link/oaxk6z/video/2nk1k6yfqe871/player&quot;&gt;18 seconds demo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Customizable video templates [Pixiko🔝] are already on ProductHunt]]></title><description><![CDATA[It has been about 2 months since we finalized our 🎬editor to the Evolution
version🎬 and reached a completely new level in video creation and editing.
During this period, we received a lot of positive feedback on video effects and
text animation, which is used by every 5th user of the service.

But…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/oau88t/customizable_video_templates_pixiko_are_already/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/oau88t/customizable_video_templates_pixiko_are_already/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 11:31:35 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;It has been about 2 months since we finalized our 🎬&lt;strong&gt;editor to the Evolution version&lt;/strong&gt;🎬 and reached a completely new level in video creation and editing. During this period, we received &lt;em&gt;a lot of positive feedback on video effects and text animation&lt;/em&gt;, which is used by every 5th user of the service.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But there were also problems with the speed of video generation, which were partially solved, and, I am sure, will be completely solved in the coming months of work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, we do not stand still and, in addition to some cosmetic and technical issues, we are trying to solve more conceptual problems.&lt;br/&gt;
And today we are glad to present you our new functionality - 🛠 customizable video templates. The main advantage of our solution is that they:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;templates are easy to create and edit at 💯;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;quickly customize to your corporate identity and company brand;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;generated for the format (💻, 🖥, 📺, 📟, etc.) of all well-known social networks and video hosting.&lt;br/&gt;
It is also convenient to make a whole bunch of videos using a prepared template by quickly replacing elements in the editor.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We ask you to support us🤝on the day of release on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.producthunt.com/posts/online-video-templates-by-pixiko-com&quot;&gt;ProductHunt&lt;/a&gt; 💪 and leave a feedback or review about our service, cause we are very sensitive to changes in the editor and bring the level of service to the maximum.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I made a markdown editor that automatically recognizes tasks/events and adds them to google calendar.]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/oarzx0/i_made_a_markdown_editor_that_automatically/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/oarzx0/i_made_a_markdown_editor_that_automatically/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 09:58:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I made blocs : notion widgets for habit building | Looking for feedback]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/oar3qx/i_made_blocs_notion_widgets_for_habit_building/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/oar3qx/i_made_blocs_notion_widgets_for_habit_building/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 07:49:03 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[My daily podcast about trying to turn side projects into businesses]]></title><description><![CDATA[A while ago I decided to quit my job and focus 💯 in my side projects in hopes
to someday make a paycheck and be able to live from them. I am narrating my
journey in a podcast where I share my conquers and frustrations and interview
other entrepreneurs in the same situation.

Here is the pilot…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/oajrh7/my_daily_podcast_about_trying_to_turn_side/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/oajrh7/my_daily_podcast_about_trying_to_turn_side/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 02:56:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A while ago I decided to quit my job and focus 💯 in my side projects in hopes to someday make a paycheck and be able to live from them. I am narrating my journey in a podcast where I share my conquers and frustrations and interview other entrepreneurs in the same situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is the pilot episode: &lt;a href=&quot;https://anchor.fm/wannabentrepreneur/episodes/1---Pilot-e10p1ba&quot;&gt;https://anchor.fm/wannabentrepreneur/episodes/1---Pilot-e10p1ba&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Would love to have your feedback. Cheers&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[After starring too many Github awesome repos, I found that I need to track them, not just star them. So I created trackawesomelist.com]]></title><description><![CDATA[I tracked 500+ most popular awesome repos, updated daily, for free.

For browsing awesome repos on Github, I have two pain points, one is that I
can't see the latest added items, and the second is that I can't see the star
count of the items, so I created trackawesomelist.com and solved my own…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/oa78w1/after_starring_too_many_github_awesome_repos_i/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/oa78w1/after_starring_too_many_github_awesome_repos_i/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 22:24:55 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I tracked 500+ most popular awesome repos, updated daily, for free.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For browsing awesome repos on Github, I have two pain points, one is that I can&amp;#39;t see the latest added items, and the second is that I can&amp;#39;t see the star count of the items, so I created trackawesomelist.com and solved my own pain points, I wonder if you also have these pain points.&lt;br/&gt;
Site: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.trackawesomelist.com&quot;&gt;https://www.trackawesomelist.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
Twitter: &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/trackawesome&quot;&gt;https://twitter.com/trackawesome&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
Telegram: &lt;a href=&quot;https://t.me/trackawesomelist&quot;&gt;https://t.me/trackawesomelist&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
If this also solves your problem, you can also upvote it for me on product hunt, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.producthunt.com/posts/track-awesome-list&quot;&gt;https://www.producthunt.com/posts/track-awesome-list&lt;/a&gt; thanks!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I made an app to make people smile!]]></title><description><![CDATA[I recently developed an app that is based around happiness and only showing
positive news, as well as jokes and cute videos of animals.

Especially during a time like this where headlines are full of negativity and
millions of people struggle with their mental health, I wanted to make an app
that…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/oac0vb/i_made_an_app_to_make_people_smile/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/oac0vb/i_made_an_app_to_make_people_smile/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 21:36:07 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I recently developed an app that is based around happiness and only showing positive news, as well as jokes and cute videos of animals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Especially during a time like this where headlines are full of negativity and millions of people struggle with their mental health, I wanted to make an app that could brighten someone&amp;#39;s day by making them smile.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The app uses a sentiment analysis AI algorithm that I developed to filter out the negativity and only show positive stories.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It would mean the world to me if you could take a moment out of your day and download the app, and if anyone has any feedback I would love to hear it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is the website: &lt;a href=&quot;https://lapisnews.tech/&quot;&gt;lapisnews.tech&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;App Store: &lt;a href=&quot;https://apps.apple.com/us/app/lapis-news-only-the-good-news/id1527590034&quot;&gt;https://apps.apple.com/us/app/lapis-news-only-the-good-news/id1527590034&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope you have a great day :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ManaMoney: manage your finances has never been so simple]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hi, I invite you to try ManaMoney.me. It's a new money manager provided as a
fully responsive Web App (and PWA) that I've developed in my spare time.

In total, the app needed seven months of development to reach the current MVP
status. The app is now ready for the closed beta.

On the homepage, you…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/oab31c/manamoney_manage_your_finances_has_never_been_so/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/oab31c/manamoney_manage_your_finances_has_never_been_so/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 20:54:36 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi, I invite you to try ManaMoney.me. It&amp;#39;s a new money manager provided as a fully responsive Web App (and PWA) that I&amp;#39;ve developed in my spare time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In total, the app needed seven months of development to reach the current MVP status. The app is now ready for the closed beta.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the homepage, you can have a full overview of the application: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.manamoney.me&quot;&gt;https://www.manamoney.me&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IMPORTANT DISCLAIMER&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Currently this is an MVP (minimum viable product), so I invite you to NOT SAVE personal information and to NOT USE IT AS YOUR MAIN MONEY MANAGER. If the app will gain interest, it will be subjected to a general security check before making it public.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/y9csnk3r68871.png?width=801&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=a3877bdc5136e35552a832d6294fa5ab83b5f139&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/y9csnk3r68871.png?width=801&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=a3877bdc5136e35552a832d6294fa5ab83b5f139&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What it does?&lt;/strong&gt; It&amp;#39;s a money manager with a minimalistic interface and a lot of peculiar features. Basically, you can use it to keep track of all your transactions (incomes/outcomes), categorize them, and analyze your current and future economic situation in the analytics section. All the cooler features are listed on the homepage with some illustrations, so if you are interested, please check the link up above.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.redd.it/d300cgax78871.gif&quot;&gt;https://i.redd.it/d300cgax78871.gif&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Languages&lt;/strong&gt; At the moment, ManaMoney is available only in the English language (and there are a lot of improvements to do on this aspect. Unfortunately I am not a native speaker). Other languages will be implemented in the future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Everything for free?!&lt;/strong&gt; The web application is available for free and probably it will forever be. You can signup by email/password or with your Google account, no payment is needed. In the future, the app will provide also an optional Premium Subscription that unlocks some cool features (already developed) like:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;SHARED-ACCOUNT(*)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;RECURRENT TRANSACTIONS(*)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;BUDGET ESTIMATION(*)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently, the Premium Status is only available for all selected beta testers that will receive the Premium Subscription for free (limited time). If there will be interest in this app, after the beta-testing phase I will open the Premium Subscription to all users (price and conditions aren&amp;#39;t defined yet).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you want to become a beta tester&lt;/strong&gt; Right now, the application is young and I think that is really premature to open all premium features to everyone. Before doing this big step, it&amp;#39;s extremely important to get some important feedback from real users, improve the application, and, only after that, there will be a reason to open all features to everyone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you want to become a beta tester, try the application first, and, if you feel that you can contribute to the product growth, please:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fill in the Beta Tester form: &lt;a href=&quot;https://forms.gle/N2PZwyRwQxkv6V2XA&quot;&gt;https://forms.gle/N2PZwyRwQxkv6V2XA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Subscribe and start to share feedback/tips/suggestions on to the ManaMoney reddit community &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/manamoney/&quot;&gt;https://www.reddit.com/r/manamoney/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not all requests on the Beta Testing Program will be accepted obviously. Also keep in mind that joining in the  beta testing program will entail some activities like filling form, share feedback, etc. Ask to become a beta tester only if you really want to be part of this :D&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/duzb4xiz78871.png?width=801&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=7bf3feb91d20bccb46749f0f01ad873bbde678cd&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/duzb4xiz78871.png?width=801&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=7bf3feb91d20bccb46749f0f01ad873bbde678cd&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to share feedback&lt;/strong&gt; If you want to share a suggestion or report a bug, you can use all information stored in the application footer. Or, if you want to be actively part of this project, please subscribe to the Reddit community &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/manamoney&quot;&gt;https://www.reddit.com/r/manamoney&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;It&amp;#39;s safe to store personal information?!&lt;/strong&gt; Like any other application, your data will be stored in an online database. Data breaches occur daily on the internet even to billionaire companies. I&amp;#39;ve done all the possible to make it as secure as possible, but I am not specialized in the security sector. Please, check the disclaimer at the beginning of the post.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What next&lt;/strong&gt; This is a side project with ZERO BUDGET. So, things will be plenty slow at the beginning. The application is complete and has all the main features that I would ask a Money Manager. The intention is to make it grow with new features and improvements during next months. You can check the &lt;a href=&quot;https://trello.com/b/daB4tVuz/manamoney-roadmap&quot;&gt;ManaMoney&amp;#39;s Roadmap on Trello&lt;/a&gt;. If you aren&amp;#39;t interested to try the application in this state of MVP, please, &lt;a href=&quot;https://gmail.us6.list-manage.com/subscribe/post?u=4c169224b5b97a598fbd6ecb7&amp;amp;id=e99591aa13&quot;&gt;Subscribe to ManaMoney&amp;#39;s newsletter to receive future updates.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2&gt;Question and Answer&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have any question, I am at your complete disposal! :D Thanks for your time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Built a tool that uses AI (GPT-3) to generate tailored resumes automatically]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/oaa3fw/built_a_tool_that_uses_ai_gpt3_to_generate/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/oaa3fw/built_a_tool_that_uses_ai_gpt3_to_generate/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 16:25:28 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[AI-powered app to make you happier! Live on Product Hunt now]]></title><description><![CDATA[We always see data being well-utilized in businesses, so that our team was
wondering - why don't we see extensive applications of data in our daily lives?

That's why we are building lyfe.ltd which we hope will become your personal
buddy-interface between you and the mountains of data that you…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/oa2ypj/aipowered_app_to_make_you_happier_live_on_product/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/oa2ypj/aipowered_app_to_make_you_happier_live_on_product/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 15:37:42 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;We always see data being well-utilized in businesses, so that our team was wondering - why don&amp;#39;t we see extensive applications of data in our daily lives?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That&amp;#39;s why we are building lyfe.ltd which we hope will become your personal buddy-interface between you and the mountains of data that you generate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;Its main features are:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;✨Mood, activity, and anything tracking&lt;br/&gt;
✨NLP powered journal&lt;br/&gt;
✨Very UI/UX friendly dashboard that displays all the correlations and AI-powered insights&lt;br/&gt;
✨ .. And much more - check out on lyfe.ltf&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/vz2gu9hxj5871.png?width=1852&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=4f8bd201fc15cb723eb6eddecf265add8fa4b542&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/vz2gu9hxj5871.png?width=1852&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=4f8bd201fc15cb723eb6eddecf265add8fa4b542&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, privacy is absolutely not an afterthought for us -- we promise to keep your data well secured and anonymized.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We want to make this product great. And great for you, not for us founders who are assuming things about its users. So your feedback is crucial on this stage and we will appreciate it a ton.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://url3173.lyfe.ltd/ls/click?upn=s74nntl2rGoHZnEr9JDcXl9lxCIZnm1g1D9TvVXV9h-2BnxGuL0iemboGQnua-2BHcDV8D9HTYT9RBNX-2FJecfTeAnQ-3D-3Ddy3n_JWL6TBCB0mED2wMiQenHzP-2BMwWyMHXmoYi3lO0xWIgWXHJLShk8qQg5V2zdXRpav0BCct5rNHoDAs-2F7dR2XWoGJkqT1kj5C1FvpImRE1izHUEM2SdZJVUjjD5PyqtPNySREn16IS8bpoDGnDGY5YWANZgainDJ0FBmWSsvPHdSmwJ0l78xhwoOvFvf6BLuCzk551684Rgg-2Fji-2BiLmNJXKynWHcruXOm75f2ZQY8Z0TVKYV7zncHVYp4ybDX9Ru-2Bf6lzv-2FEri8Vqf-2Fn0nLYbQPg-3D-3D&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Upvote Lyfe&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;strong&gt;on Product Hunt&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, if you have any feedback or thoughts - let us know below!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I have just launched for the first time on Product Hunt! 🥳 [identid.me]]]></title><description><![CDATA[After months of 12-hour workdays, we finally launched on Product Hunt!

https://www.producthunt.com/posts/identid-me

We all pursue a dream, but achieving it is not an easy task. We have created
identid.me to help creatives stand out from the crowd and have the online
portfolio that really shows…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/oa68ih/i_have_just_launched_for_the_first_time_on/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/oa68ih/i_have_just_launched_for_the_first_time_on/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 15:11:39 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;After months of 12-hour workdays, we finally launched on Product Hunt!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.producthunt.com/posts/identid-me&quot;&gt;https://www.producthunt.com/posts/identid-me&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We all pursue a dream, but achieving it is not an easy task. We have created identid.me to help creatives stand out from the crowd and have the online portfolio that really shows what they are made of. 🚀&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Feel free to create your free portfolio and give us your honest opinion to help us improve. 💛&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;PS: Also, I&amp;#39;ll be posting through the day how everything is going on and what we learn from all this in this thread: &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/identidme/status/1409771022925053952&quot;&gt;https://twitter.com/identidme/status/1409771022925053952&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[WaterMe - Plant Care App : An app to help you organize your plants, garden, veggies, bonsai, etc!]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hi everyone,

The early access version of my app is now on the Play Store! It's designed to
help you organize and track your plants and was completed using Flutter/Dart. It
has a multitude of features with many more in the pipeline. Would be grateful to
anyone that checks it out! Happy to receive…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o9vxit/waterme_plant_care_app_an_app_to_help_you/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o9vxit/waterme_plant_care_app_an_app_to_help_you/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 09:22:01 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi everyone,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The early access version of my app is now on the Play Store! It&amp;#39;s designed to help you organize and track your plants and was completed using Flutter/Dart. It has a multitude of features with many more in the pipeline. Would be grateful to anyone that checks it out! Happy to receive pros and cons so that I know where it excels and where I can do better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Feel free to check it out here:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.waterme.app&quot;&gt;https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.waterme.app&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[An alternative to Google Dictionary extension]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/oa2wgl/an_alternative_to_google_dictionary_extension/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/oa2wgl/an_alternative_to_google_dictionary_extension/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 08:25:00 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[After 1 year and 3 months, I have finally launched the Pro version of my data visualisation software.]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o9hdo0/after_1_year_and_3_months_i_have_finally_launched/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o9hdo0/after_1_year_and_3_months_i_have_finally_launched/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 13:32:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Compare cost of living in 1000 cities in the world based on your lifestyle]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hi,

Let me share with you a project I created mostly for fun. I am currently looking
for monetization ideas though - so will appreciate your ideas and any feedback
really!

I myself have moved to a different country a few times, and likely not the last
time in my life. And I've found it quite…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o973xy/compare_cost_of_living_in_1000_cities_in_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o973xy/compare_cost_of_living_in_1000_cities_in_the/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 01:05:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me share with you a project I created mostly for fun. I am currently looking for monetization ideas though - so will appreciate your ideas and any feedback really!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I myself have moved to a different country a few times, and likely not the last time in my life. And I&amp;#39;ve found it quite difficult to compare not consumer prices, say, for tomatoes or a 2-bed apartment, but my lifestyle as a whole, including how many people are moving, what habits we have, and what services we use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To address the issue, I built this calculator: &lt;a href=&quot;https://gromov.com/cost-of-living-calc?utm_source=reddit_sideproj&quot;&gt;https://gromov.com/cost-of-living-calc&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;⚠️It currently doesn&amp;#39;t work on mobile devices (WIP), so please use desktop version.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other than that, it shall be fairly straightforward and hopefully fun to use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me know what you think!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cheers,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oleg&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[My first finished project: Reveal fun insights from WhatsApp chats]]></title><description><![CDATA[Finally fought my distractions and saw a side project through completion. Using
GatsbyJS, ReactJS, ChartJS, I created a simple web app that analyzes fun
insights from WhatsApp chats into pretty graphs plus sentiment analysis and word
cloud. No ads, no user registrations/logins, no monetization…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o8y90x/my_first_finished_project_reveal_fun_insights/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o8y90x/my_first_finished_project_reveal_fun_insights/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 21:29:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally fought my distractions and saw a side project through completion. Using GatsbyJS, ReactJS, ChartJS, I created a simple web app that analyzes fun insights from WhatsApp chats into pretty graphs plus sentiment analysis and word cloud. 
No ads, no user registrations/logins, no monetization aspirations, just something fun to start and complete. Was inspired by this community and welcome all feedback 👍
Link: &lt;a href=&quot;https://whatstats.io/&quot;&gt;https://whatstats.io/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Made a song that plants trees]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o8t8y1/made_a_song_that_plants_trees/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o8t8y1/made_a_song_that_plants_trees/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jun 2021 17:32:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Command Line Tool for REACT applications]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hi, everyone!
I am happy to share my recent small utility project with you all. It is a
command-line tool that helps developers to automate some obvious tasks like
scaffolding a new react application and generating a new component. It supports
both typescript & javascript templates.

Refer to the…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o8d3x2/command_line_tool_for_react_applications/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o8d3x2/command_line_tool_for_react_applications/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 18:51:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi, everyone!&lt;br/&gt;
I am happy to share my recent small &lt;strong&gt;utility project&lt;/strong&gt; with you all. It is a &lt;strong&gt;command-line tool&lt;/strong&gt; that helps developers to automate some obvious tasks like &lt;strong&gt;scaffolding a new react application and generating a new component&lt;/strong&gt;. It supports both typescript &amp;amp; javascript templates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Refer to the video to see how it works :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://reddit.com/link/o8d3x2/video/kirg0f2gpm771/player&quot;&gt;React CLI Utility Demo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NPM Package: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.npmjs.com/package/react-cli-utility&quot;&gt;https://www.npmjs.com/package/react-cli-utility&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;
Github: &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/hvg2416/react-cli&quot;&gt;https://github.com/hvg2416/react-cli&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me know what more improvements &amp;amp; features I may work on.&lt;br/&gt;
Thanks in advance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[An honest reflection on the first two rollercoaster months of building up my SaaS.]]></title><description><![CDATA[Ngl, I’m pretty excited to share this reflection with y’all.

Predis.ai was launched just over 2 months ago, and we thought of taking some
time off to reflect on the journey, and determine what worked well and what
didn’t (we really weren’t prepared for how many things did not work :’))

Predis is…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o86jnk/an_honest_reflection_on_the_first_two/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o86jnk/an_honest_reflection_on_the_first_two/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:56:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ngl, I’m pretty excited to share this reflection with y’all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Predis.ai was launched just over 2 months ago, and we thought of taking some time off to reflect on the journey, and determine what worked well and what didn’t (we really weren’t prepared for how many things did not work :’))&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Predis is essentially an AI/ML-based SaaS that predicts a social media post’s performance before it is posted, so it can be improved with the AI’s suggestions. Influencers and brands can also carry out comprehensive competitor analysis on Predis to understand the kind of content that is working well for them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I basically divided this blog into 4 distinct sections:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- Why we changed our target platform from Twitter to Instagram&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- How our Product Hunt launch fared (spoiler: not very well)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- Our LTD offering on Pitchground&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;- Key learnings from some user metrics&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can check out the Medium blog &lt;a href=&quot;https://medium.com/predisai/predis-ai-2-months-overview-apr-may-2021-db9180f711fd&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;! Hoping this will provide useful insights to new founders about what to expect when at the helm of a SaaS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Good luck, side-hustlers!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Got around to launching my app for iOS. Efficiently track your day’s ups and downs! Want to hear your thoughts.]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o7x434/got_around_to_launching_my_app_for_ios/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o7x434/got_around_to_launching_my_app_for_ios/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 14:14:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[We created Rethink Files, a file browser that connects and unifies all your clouds. You can search, organize and share files regardless of where they are stored. We are in public beta and currently have 19 integrations (with more to come!), including Google Drive, OneDrive, Slack, Figma & Basecamp.]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o7q8z9/we_created_rethink_files_a_file_browser_that/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o7q8z9/we_created_rethink_files_a_file_browser_that/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 18:52:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[My favorite resources for solo founders]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hi folks,

I want to introduce an app I've been working on and as a quick "thank you" for
your time, I'm listing the most valuable resources for solo startup founders I
found:

 * Product Disrupt [https://productdisrupt.com/] - Curated List of Resources to
   Learn Product Design
 * ManyPixels…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o7fodu/my_favorite_resources_for_solo_founders/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o7fodu/my_favorite_resources_for_solo_founders/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 15:28:57 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi folks,&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to introduce an app I&amp;#39;ve been working on and as a quick &amp;quot;thank you&amp;quot; for your time, I&amp;#39;m listing the most valuable resources for solo startup founders I found:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://productdisrupt.com/&quot;&gt;Product Disrupt&lt;/a&gt; - Curated List of Resources to Learn Product Design&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.manypixels.co/gallery&quot;&gt;ManyPixels&lt;/a&gt; - Free illustrations for commercial use&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://reallygoodemails.com/&quot;&gt;Really Good emails&lt;/a&gt; - Awesome curated collection of email templates&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://startuplanding.redq.io/&quot;&gt;Startup Landing&lt;/a&gt; - A list of free landing page templates for React, Gatsby &amp;amp; Next.js&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://builtformars.com/&quot;&gt;Built For Mars&lt;/a&gt; - A list of great UX case studies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/goabstract/Marketing-for-Engineers&quot;&gt;Marketing for Engineers&lt;/a&gt; - A curated list of articles and tools to grow your product&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now back to my app. YourTrail is a personal assistant to plan, track and achieve your goals and aspirations. I just finished building an MVP and would love to hear your thoughts about the MVP and the idea in general. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can check out YourTrail here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://yourtrail.io&quot;&gt;https://yourtrail.io&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The app lets you plan your life goals, organize your book notes and other learnings, and connect them with your goals. It will also have a suite of productivity tools like streaks (habit building), timeboxed working sessions &amp;amp; daily reminders to help you take small daily steps towards your goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Using YourTrail, you can break down complex goals into simple, actionable steps and have fun doing it. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Any feedback and comments are greatly appreciated!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Permanent and Immutable Cloud Storage for files that you cannot afford to lose.]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://preview.redd.it/v4mor8tb4d771.png?width=1891&format=png&auto=webp&s=68a2fd969ee3828cee2cee37302de25baba1c191

Hi! I am thrilled to announce that I've launched Forever.so [https://Forever.so]
- permanent and immutable cloud storage.

It's a place where you can safely store your precious files…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o7ioxa/permanent_and_immutable_cloud_storage_for_files/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o7ioxa/permanent_and_immutable_cloud_storage_for_files/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 08:14:22 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/v4mor8tb4d771.png?width=1891&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=68a2fd969ee3828cee2cee37302de25baba1c191&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/v4mor8tb4d771.png?width=1891&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=68a2fd969ee3828cee2cee37302de25baba1c191&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hi! I am thrilled to announce that I&amp;#39;ve launched &lt;a href=&quot;https://Forever.so&quot;&gt;Forever.so&lt;/a&gt; - &lt;strong&gt;permanent and immutable cloud storage&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It&amp;#39;s a place where you can safely store your precious files without ever worrying about losing them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a way to &amp;quot;scratch my own itch&amp;quot; (I&amp;#39;ve lost invaluable family photos before), and after a decade of waiting for a solution, I&amp;#39;ve funded and spent 1,500+ hours on building it myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://Forever.so&quot;&gt;Forever.so&lt;/a&gt; is protecting your or your company&amp;#39;s most valuable files. Permanent means secure!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can check it out here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://Forever.so&quot;&gt;Forever.so&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[After being frustrated with other note-taking apps, I made Capcha, the fastest note-taking app in the world!]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o71bi0/after_being_frustrated_with_other_notetaking_apps/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o71bi0/after_being_frustrated_with_other_notetaking_apps/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 15:27:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I spent 2 years making this app, and released the first beta version yesterday. It uses Al to scan your screenshots for usernames and links. Also has a built in website builder. Please give me feedback!]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o70fuv/i_spent_2_years_making_this_app_and_released_the/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o70fuv/i_spent_2_years_making_this_app_and_released_the/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 14:58:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[💬 No more messy Slack conversations: We created a free Slack add-on that helps you turn Slack into a knowledge base]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o6fft3/no_more_messy_slack_conversations_we_created_a/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o6fft3/no_more_messy_slack_conversations_we_created_a/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 18:43:53 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I built a doorbell that scares people]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o6dwxs/i_built_a_doorbell_that_scares_people/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o6dwxs/i_built_a_doorbell_that_scares_people/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 16:30:18 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I built Feynman, a spaced repetition flashcard application with handwriting recognition for practicing the Feynman technique to understand difficult concepts]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o5zn0r/i_built_feynman_a_spaced_repetition_flashcard/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o5zn0r/i_built_feynman_a_spaced_repetition_flashcard/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Jun 2021 13:24:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I'm building an app to write interactive blog posts from the browser. It lets you add markdown and custom/pre-built react components inside your posts.]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o5tz5h/im_building_an_app_to_write_interactive_blog/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o5tz5h/im_building_an_app_to_write_interactive_blog/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 22:20:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[A murder mystery game side project]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o5q7ob/a_murder_mystery_game_side_project/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o5q7ob/a_murder_mystery_game_side_project/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 17:48:34 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I built a streaming aggregator to access free streaming on Netflix, Amazon, HBO]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://onestreamtv.com/

Hey guys, OneStream TV is a streaming aggregator that allows you to have free
streaming access on content on Netflix, Amazon Prime Video, HBO Max, and many
other streaming services, without subscribing to any service or paying money.

I know what you're thinking: "Is this…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o5luoi/i_built_a_streaming_aggregator_to_access_free/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o5luoi/i_built_a_streaming_aggregator_to_access_free/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 17:16:50 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://onestreamtv.com/&quot;&gt;https://onestreamtv.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hey guys, OneStream TV is a streaming aggregator that allows you to have free streaming access on content on Netflix, Amazon Prime Video, HBO Max, and many other streaming services, without subscribing to any service or paying money.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know what you&amp;#39;re thinking: &amp;quot;Is this legal?&amp;quot;. Answer is yes, 100% legal :). Many streaming services provide free access (without requiring subscription) to a limited number of their content as part of their holistic marketing strategy, but these free content are randomly provided by streaming services because they&amp;#39;re usually part of some complex promotional marketing strategy, which means it&amp;#39;s hard for the average consumer to easily discover and access the content. So OneStream TV solves this problem programmatically by automatically monitoring, indexing, and aggregating all the free content being provided by all the major streaming services and combining them in one unified streaming dashboard.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m posting this here mainly to get you guys&amp;#39; feedback and reaction, so please let me know what you guys think, if you like it (any feature requests), or if you think I should shut it down :-).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/9ikvmk8s7t671.jpg?width=1440&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=182e938118dcfb7c5cd21077cdf4e8ea78e7f42b&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/9ikvmk8s7t671.jpg?width=1440&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=182e938118dcfb7c5cd21077cdf4e8ea78e7f42b&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/n24zabkt7t671.jpg?width=1543&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=6c90250e7485fcac9a817a5abfa141a681629c81&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/n24zabkt7t671.jpg?width=1543&amp;amp;format=pjpg&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=6c90250e7485fcac9a817a5abfa141a681629c81&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I made a bookmarking app that can save and discover bite-sized learning resources related to tech.]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o5onv2/i_made_a_bookmarking_app_that_can_save_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o5onv2/i_made_a_bookmarking_app_that_can_save_and/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 16:44:02 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[We've just released our first app: "Then — Activity & Mood Diary". It's a simple, clean, and calming app that helps you analyze how you spend your time and how things you do influence your emotions. Available now for iOS: pupishi.com/then]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o5hmj6/weve_just_released_our_first_app_then_activity/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o5hmj6/weve_just_released_our_first_app_then_activity/</guid><pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 09:41:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I've asked 750+ startup founders. "How did you come up with your idea?" Here are their answers:]]></title><description><![CDATA[First, they most commonly say:

"Solve your own problems. Meaning, live on the edge of tech and see what issues
you encounter. Then build a startup to solve it."

I agree, and I love that.

But it's not the whole answer you want. Where do these problems actually come
from?

1) I’ll start by defining…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o54iaj/ive_asked_750_startup_founders_how_did_you_come/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o54iaj/ive_asked_750_startup_founders_how_did_you_come/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 21:39:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;First, they most commonly say:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Solve your own problems. Meaning, live on the edge of tech and see what issues you encounter. Then build a startup to solve it.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I agree, and I love that.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But it&amp;#39;s not the whole answer you want. Where do these problems actually come from?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;I’ll start by defining what a good startup idea looks like to me.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It offers a meaningful benefit, such as:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• A big reduction of an intense/frequent frustration&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• A big reduction in the cost of an expensive problem&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• A big increase in how entertaining/emotional a thing is&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;2) I call these 3x ideas&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;— ideas compelling enough to overcome the friction to try &amp;#39;em. Btw, some people say startups must be &amp;quot;10x better to succeed.&amp;quot; This is misleading.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For an app to be 10x better, than, say, Uber, it would have to straight up teleport you to your destination.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;3) Examples of real 3x ideas:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Dropbox/Box: Cheaply share files without coordination or friction&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Instacart: Get groceries delivered—without a big cost premium&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Uber: Get a cab 3x faster, in 3x more locations, and for cheaper&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;4) So, where do these 3x ideas come from?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;From the creation of new infrastructure—either technological or legal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I keep an eye on this. For example:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;New technologies&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Fast mobile processors&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• High-capacity batteries&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Cryptocurrency architecture&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• VR&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;2. Changes in the law&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Legalization of marijuana&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Patents expiring (And 1,000 more infrastructure examples.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;When new technological/legal infrastructure emerges, startups pounce to productize the new 3x possibilities.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Those possibilities fall into categories:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;1. Cost reductions:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Cheaper broadband enables cloud storage (Dropbox)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Cheaper batteries enables electric cars (Tesla)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;2. Better functionality:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Smartphones and 3G spawned the mobile era&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;3. Brand new categories:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• The legalization of marijuana spawned weed stores and weed delivery apps (And more.)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So takeaway number one is that new infrastructure spawns startups.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;5)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;strong&gt;But, we&amp;#39;re not done.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For those ideas to survive in the market, I believe you need another criterion:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cultural acceptance. Society has to be ready for you:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here are startups that became possible through changes in societal behavior.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;1. Pop culture making behaviors less cool:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Cigarettes go out of style, so we get nicotine and vaping&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• Heavy drinking goes out of style, so we get low-alcohol seltzers&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;2. Mobile apps making it more normal to trust strangers:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;• The rise of Uber, Airbnb, Tinder, and couchsurfing better acclimated society to trusting people they’ve only met over the Internet. This next part is important:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;6) Implication&lt;/strong&gt;: Study changes in infrastructure plus shifts in cultural acceptance to identify what’s newly possible in your market. Here&amp;#39;s an example:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Uber saw that widespread smartphone adoption with accurate GPS data made it possible to replace taxis with gig workers.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cultural acceptance was needed here—because it was unorthodox to step into a stranger&amp;#39;s car and entrust them with your safety.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;7) Okay, so let&amp;#39;s turn all this into a framework.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;#39;s just one way to find startup ideas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Step 1: Spot upcoming infrastructure&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Step 2: Determine if market entry is now possible&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Step 3: Explore second-order ideas too&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;8) Second, when another startup captures a 3x benefit,&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;it typically produces many downstream 2x ideas.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a key point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, now that millions use 3x products like Slack, Zoom, and Uber, what tools could make them less expensive, more reliable, more collaborative?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;9) To recap:&lt;/strong&gt; One way to find startup ideas is to study infrastructure (3x ideas) and observe what emerges from startups that tackle that infrastructure (2x ideas).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;💡 Tip:&lt;/em&gt; If you enjoyed this then maybe I can tempt you with my Twitter page where I write daily insights on startups investing like this. &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/__Uplift&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Learn more →&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I've built Moodmonk, an app that helps you get into a positive mood with daily reflections, positive affirmations, and hundreds of exercises! Available now for iOS: moodmonk.app]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o4sk84/ive_built_moodmonk_an_app_that_helps_you_get_into/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o4sk84/ive_built_moodmonk_an_app_that_helps_you_get_into/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 20:11:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[We've recently built a simple application that helps you automatically brand your business, idea or side project, and manage it on-going! It's called brandsynth.com. Feedback would be much appreciated :) (And potentially rewarded!)]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o4odkf/weve_recently_built_a_simple_application_that/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o4odkf/weve_recently_built_a_simple_application_that/</guid><pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 08:57:37 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[We've built a simple minimalistic app to organize your life. It's called Organize Your Life (OYL) Feedback much appreciated 👉🏾 oylapp.com]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o49ieh/weve_built_a_simple_minimalistic_app_to_organize/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o49ieh/weve_built_a_simple_minimalistic_app_to_organize/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 19:12:13 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[A personal TIME MANAGER that arranges your time into WORK, BREAKS & FREETIME.]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o3wz1u/a_personal_time_manager_that_arranges_your_time/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o3wz1u/a_personal_time_manager_that_arranges_your_time/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 06:29:27 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Better Linktree Link In Bio Alternative for Creators]]></title><description><![CDATA[Couple friends and I built a link in bio product to help creators better display
their content, increase conversion, and track analytics across social media
channels all on one link.

Would love to get your guys' thoughts: bytesize.me [https://bytesize.me/]

Example: https://bytesize.me/postmalone]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o3pwjg/better_linktree_link_in_bio_alternative_for/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o3pwjg/better_linktree_link_in_bio_alternative_for/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 03:27:58 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Couple friends and I built a link in bio product to help creators better display their content, increase conversion, and track analytics across social media channels all on one link.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Would love to get your guys&amp;#39; thoughts: &lt;a href=&quot;https://bytesize.me/&quot;&gt;bytesize.me&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Example: &lt;a href=&quot;https://bytesize.me/postmalone&quot;&gt;https://bytesize.me/postmalone&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I made a web app to convert tweets into images for sharing on social media - snaptweets.com]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o3bj63/i_made_a_web_app_to_convert_tweets_into_images/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o3bj63/i_made_a_web_app_to_convert_tweets_into_images/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 19:25:43 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Algorithmic booty maximiser]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o345sy/algorithmic_booty_maximiser/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o345sy/algorithmic_booty_maximiser/</guid><pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2021 02:59:38 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I have made a Table Hole game called "Color Hole & Blocks". Please let me know what you think about it.]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o2om0l/i_have_made_a_table_hole_game_called_color_hole/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o2om0l/i_have_made_a_table_hole_game_called_color_hole/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 20:40:45 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[We made a website where you can record 4K video podcasts!]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o2q6lp/we_made_a_website_where_you_can_record_4k_video/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o2q6lp/we_made_a_website_where_you_can_record_4k_video/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 18:33:19 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Automatic Online Bankroll Management Tracker]]></title><description><![CDATA[There are currently a number of poker software solutions that allow you to do
this by logging each session of live or online poker -- I have been working on
making an online bankroll tracker which would automatically collect this session
data allowing users to easily track and analyze your poker…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o2lnzt/automatic_online_bankroll_management_tracker/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o2lnzt/automatic_online_bankroll_management_tracker/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 13:42:31 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are currently a number of poker software solutions that allow you to do this by logging each session of live or online poker -- &lt;strong&gt;I have been working on making an online bankroll tracker which would automatically collect this session data allowing users to easily&lt;/strong&gt; track and analyze your poker performance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Features I am planning on implementing would include past session tracking, game selection controls and Bankroll variation statistics etc. including multiple currencies support, Risk of ruin calculations including both online &amp;amp; live bankrolls options for custom transactions types with direct linking between your session and transactions and the option for users specific date filtering.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;I will shortly be looking for Beta users &amp;amp; would love to get your feedback and any features you would like to be added :)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Multiverse, written by you and AI]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hello, everyone. I am a programmer and also a science fiction enthusiast. From
childhood, I am fascinated by the idea of building a real-intelligent machine,
like housekeeping-robot Andrew in the movie "Bicentennial Man" or SETTLER in
“Expelled from Paradise (Rakuen Tsuihō)”. After graduating, I…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o22dah/multiverse_written_by_you_and_ai/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o22dah/multiverse_written_by_you_and_ai/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 20:25:10 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello, everyone. I am a programmer and also a science fiction enthusiast. From childhood, I am fascinated by the idea of building a real-intelligent machine, like housekeeping-robot Andrew in the movie &amp;quot;Bicentennial Man&amp;quot; or SETTLER in “Expelled from Paradise (Rakuen Tsuihō)”. After graduating, I made a lot of practical software, but my inner flame of artificial intelligence has never been extinguished. My new app &lt;a href=&quot;https://dreamily.ai&quot;&gt;dreamily.ai&lt;/a&gt; may make it possible to see a ray of light into these dreams.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Language can plot scenes, and a language model which can predict what will happen is a world simulator. For example, you can create a scene in outer space :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Alpha Centauri, the 13th fleet of the Free Planet Alliance is moving through here very carefully.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;the AI will continue to write:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;They&amp;#39;re not sure if they want to make a big mistake and attract more attention than necessary. This is just their second attempt to find this new star system, the one that was supposedly inhabited by some sort of sentient life, but it&amp;#39;s proving unsuccessful. They&amp;#39;ve been searching for weeks now without any luck at all&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/uv81dbgdru571.png?width=2446&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=8d0ff747331e52464d38b25f5f38581b888839ce&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/uv81dbgdru571.png?width=2446&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=8d0ff747331e52464d38b25f5f38581b888839ce&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What will happen next? You can interact with AI and add a line:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Suddenly, a spaceship of unknown origin appeared on the radar&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What will happen next? in Universe #1, they hide:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Suddenly, a spaceship of unknown origin appeared on the radar and quickly moved in their direction. Their ships slowed down to avoid being noticed. After a few hours, when they were certain that the ship hadn&amp;#39;t spotted them&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/v4175j4buu571.png?width=2236&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=ec562a9ceca24c33197ed50ffc2087088d63fd9f&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/v4175j4buu571.png?width=2236&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=ec562a9ceca24c33197ed50ffc2087088d63fd9f&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;in Universe #2, they fight:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;They were ready to call in reinforcements from Alpha Centauri when the ship made a sharp turn and headed straight towards them. The sensors went crazy with warnings, and as Alpha Centauri fired on it, it disappeared into a ball of fire. It wasn&amp;#39;t long before the first wave of ships started appearing behind it.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/me82eg3iuu571.png?width=2218&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=65c761e87420aed8debed62fc8adab5746bf57ba&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/me82eg3iuu571.png?width=2218&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=65c761e87420aed8debed62fc8adab5746bf57ba&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can click &amp;quot;Go on&amp;quot; to get to the next part of the story. Or you can dive into a new magical world like:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/epji2qnhvu571.png?width=574&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=787dfdf71be8a5cf3366193970b0d4a6dc65b1af&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/epji2qnhvu571.png?width=574&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=787dfdf71be8a5cf3366193970b0d4a6dc65b1af&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can chat with your housekeeping-robot Andrew:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://preview.redd.it/jncfgtq3wu571.png?width=1422&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=eeca421b1597282705b288e6f596b61f5fda6d20&quot;&gt;https://preview.redd.it/jncfgtq3wu571.png?width=1422&amp;amp;format=png&amp;amp;auto=webp&amp;amp;s=eeca421b1597282705b288e6f596b61f5fda6d20&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The only thing that limited the ability of &lt;a href=&quot;https://dreamily.ai&quot;&gt;dreamily.ai&lt;/a&gt; is your imagination.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://dreamily.ai&quot;&gt;dreamily.ai&lt;/a&gt; is Free and Powerful, but I don&amp;#39;t know what will happen next after I post this first introduction of &lt;a href=&quot;https://dreamily.ai&quot;&gt;dreamily.ai&lt;/a&gt;. I hope you enjoy my work, create your multiverse, report bugs, improve AI together with me, and may AI makes our life better.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I made WordPress Dark Mode Plugin]]></title><description><![CDATA[https://i.redd.it/qgiwx89c8s571.gif

As the dark mode is very trendy and everyone loves to use apps/websites in dark
mode. So recently, my team developed and launch a new WordPress plugin and
already it hits 1000 active installations on wordpress.org. If you are a
WordPress user then I asked you to…]]></description><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o1rp9a/i_made_wordpress_dark_mode_plugin/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o1rp9a/i_made_wordpress_dark_mode_plugin/</guid><pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2021 13:11:56 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded>&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://i.redd.it/qgiwx89c8s571.gif&quot;&gt;https://i.redd.it/qgiwx89c8s571.gif&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the dark mode is very trendy and everyone loves to use apps/websites in dark mode. So recently, my team developed and launch a new WordPress plugin and already it hits 1000 active installations on wordpress.org.  If you are a WordPress user then I asked you to check the plugin and provide your valuable feedback.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Free download: &lt;a href=&quot;https://wordpress.org/plugins/droit-dark-mode/&quot;&gt;https://wordpress.org/plugins/droit-dark-mode/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[I made MotionMonkey 🐵, a streamlined Youtube and Torrent player based on OpenSource technologies. Available on the PlayStore.]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o107qp/i_made_motionmonkey_a_streamlined_youtube_and/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o107qp/i_made_motionmonkey_a_streamlined_youtube_and/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 13:14:26 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[3 months in: Here are the UX improvements I've made to WeWatch, my app where you swipe on movies you want to watch and find matches with your friends]]></title><link>https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o0nrdt/3_months_in_here_are_the_ux_improvements_ive_made/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">https://sideproject.buzzing.cc/reddit/r/SideProject/comments/o0nrdt/3_months_in_here_are_the_ux_improvements_ive_made/</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Jun 2021 05:53:24 GMT</pubDate><content:encoded></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>